let MCQS = [{
    question: "Which city in USA has the most population?",
    choice1: "Los Angeles",
    choice2: "Chicago",
    choice3: "New York",
    choice4: "San Diego",
    answer: 3
},           
            {
            question: "How many people live in New York?",
    choice1: "8 million",
    choice2: "20 million",
    choice3: "8.5  million",
    choice4: "5 million",
    answer: 3 
},          
            {
            question: "Which city is the world's largest by area?",
    choice1: "Tokyo",
    choice2: "Maxico City",
    choice3: "London",
    choice4: "New York",
    answer: 1 
},
             {
             question: "Which city is the largest in Germany?",
    choice1: "München",
    choice2: "Berlin",
    choice3: "Hamburg",
    choice4: "Köln",
    answer: 2
},           
             {
             question: "Which city in Europe is the most expensive to live in?",
    choice1: "Berlin",
    choice2: "London",
    choice3: "Zürich",
    choice4: "Genève",
    answer: 3
},
             {
             question: "Which city in the world has the most tourists?",
    choice1: "London",
    choice2: "Tokyo",
    choice3: "Bangkok",
    choice4: "Dubai",
    answer: 3
},   
             {
             question: "Which city in the world has the most hours of sunshine?",
    choice1: "Yuma",
    choice2: "London",
    choice3: "Paris",
    choice4: "Miami",
    answer: 1
},
             {
             question: "Which city is the capital of France?",
    choice1: "Tokyo",
    choice2: "Nice",
    choice3: "Marseille",
    choice4: "Paris",
    answer: 4
},
             {
             question: "Which city in europe has the most population?",
    choice1: "Sankt Petersburg",
    choice2: "Moskva",
    choice3: "Paris",
    choice4: "London",
    answer: 2
},
             {
             question: "Which city has the most rainy days?",
    choice1: "Cherrapunijee",
    choice2: "Tokyo",
    choice3: "London",
    choice4: "New York",
    answer: 1
}];